hey there everyone sorry this video is a
date Leigh I kind of forgot about it
because I was holding Sonic Underground
marathon but better late than never
right what do you say we get started
with final questions before we begin
I feel like I need to save this go
and buy this DVD if you love
Sokka and you love this it's only
399 go buy first question was it
difficult trying to draw all soccer
characters for the first time in your
own style or did it come naturally well
first of all it's not my own style I
draw it almost to perfection to the show
I I tried to go for a style where if you
were to look at my drawings and then
look at the actual episode of the show
you couldn't tell which one's the real
one not saying that mine's fake it's
real although basically they're both
real I just it's just that that's all it
is really my style
I draw exactly like the show and yes it
did come naturally when I first picked
up a pencil when I was a baby I saw suck
on TV then the first thought that came
to my mind was I got a drop of that
question number 2 have you ever wonder
where your life life would be without
sock on the ground we don't talk about
that question number 3 how long do
you take you to massive pain and why do
you choose that for your drawings as I
said previously I did not have to learn
math but I was already a pro at it and
why use it well we don't fix what ain't
broken am I right as you can tell I'm
doing just fine with paint there's no
reason to get anything else I mean
that'd be like telling van Gogh to aah
give up paints and in black draw
with a computer that there's no need
there's no need
question them before how many times have
you read watched bow be the prisoner
Allah question number five is a very
good question because I know a lot fuel
want to hear this question number five
how do you come up with your stories for
all your videos how they based on your
life basically this how it goes down
I'll be walking down the street I see
something happen or I'll just be sitting
at home watching TV something will come
on
and all I see I think man just imagine
how much better this would be it was the
Sonic undergone cast that would be cool
and then that's how it kind of happened
question number six are you faster than
Sonic well yeah if you watch my videos
you would know I made a video about that
she bit well that's all the questions
for the interview I guess so yeah there
you go
I don't want you know what else do for
this video side I guess I can show off
my Sonic on DVDs until my camera shuts
off as you can see I got a lot of them
you can see ten on the desk right here
although I got like a hundred and
the others are just in the back room cuz
well why the why bring a hundred
hundred DVDs put them on a desk I
mainly just brought these ten because
they're my favorite ones
so I'd like to thank all of you for
sending in these questions pretty cool
pretty cool I'm working on about dog
videos got a new animation in the works
gonna be pretty awesome get hopped in
what sock on the ground boom late
get here